Problem

The table reservation function feels unintuitive, making it difficult for users to book a table to dine in. There's no clear option to select dates and times, and the process of filling out the form feels takes a long time.

DEFINING THE PROBLEMS

How can we redesign a better experience and create a consistent interface for customers, so they can save time when ordering food?

THE GOAL

Redesign Little Lemon's website to address deficiencies such as inconsistencies in actions and design
Improve user experience and interaction with the Little Lemon App.
Making it easy for users to reserve tables and order food online.

MY ROLE

UI/UX Designer, designs products from idea to final product.

RESPONSIBILITIES

Conduct user research to create user personas and journey maps. create a workflow from start to finish, create a framework or sketch of the design and user interface features, create a design prototype